Guide to the Southern Poverty Law Center Intelligence Project Collection, 1940s-2020; 1940s-ongoing RL.10135
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Southern Poverty Law Center Intelligence Project collection
1940s-2020; 1940s-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Southern Poverty Law Center
RL.10135
115 Linear Feet 85,500 items
The SPLC Intelligence Project Collection includes printed materials, serials, organizational literature, pamphlets, clippings, catalogs, fliers, and correspondence from a variety of groups monitored by the SPLC and its contacts between the 1980s and 2010. Included within the collection are many groups falling within the SPLC Klanwatch and Militia Watch projects. Organizations represented in this collection typically promoted anti-semitic, white supremacist, racist, separatist, or anti-Communist views and policies. Other organizations promoted Second Amendment rights, right-wing Christian and American nationalism, Y2K and survivalist preparations, and the rise of the Confederacy. SPLC's interests expanded across the political spectrum to include both right-wing and left-wing extremist literature.
Arrangement
Collection is divided into two series: Organizations and SPLC Research, Subjects, and Clippings Files. There are also over 450 serial titles which have been separated from the collection and are available for request through the library catalog.
Separated Material
Over 450 serial titles have been cataloged separately from this archival collection. Click this link for a list of SPLC Intelligence Project serials in the library catalog: Separately cataloged serials
Collection Overview
The SPLC Intelligence Project Collection includes printed materials, serials, organizational literature, pamphlets, clippings, catalogs, fliers, and correspondence from a variety of groups monitored by the SPLC and its contacts between the 1980s and 2010. Included within the collection are many groups falling within the SPLC Klanwatch and Militia Watch projects. Organizations represented in this collection typically promoted anti-Semitic, white supremacist, racist, separatist, or anti-Communist views and politics. Other organizations promoted Second Amendment rights, right-wing Christian and American nationalism, Y2K and survivalist preparations, and the rise of the Confederacy. SPLC's interests expanded across the political spectrum to include both right-wing and left-wing extremist literature.
The manuscript portion of the collection includes 11.0 lin. ft. of materials; the remainder of the collection, consisting of serials collected by SPLC from various organizations, has been separated for individual cataloging.
Check the library catalog link for a list of separated serial titles: Separately cataloged serials
Historical Note
The Southern Poverty Law Center is based in Montgomery, Alabama.
Provenance
The Southern Poverty Law Center Intelligence Project Collection was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2013.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Related Materials
See also the Evelyn Rich Papers and the Ku Klux Klan Collection, held in Rubenstein Library.
Racism -- United States; Left-wing extremists -- United States.; Conspiracy theories -- United States.; Conservative literature -- United States.; Antisemitism in literature -- United States.; Holocaust denial literature -- United States.; Gun control -- United States; United States -- Immigration policy.; Right-wing extremists -- United States.; Year 2000 date conversion (Computer systems) -- United States.; Alternative publications -- United States; Survivalist literature -- United States.; United States -- Economic policy; White supremacy movements -- United States; Anglo-Israelism -- United States; Neo-Nazis -- United States.; Nazis -- United States.; States' rights (American politics) -- Southern States.; Klanwatch Project.; Ku Klux Klan (1915- ); Intelligence Project; Human Rights Archive (Duke University); Catholic Church; Southern Poverty Law Center; Invisible Empire, Knights of the Ku Klux Klan (1975); Knights of the Ku Klux Klan (1975); Duke, David Ernest; Miller, Glenn, 1940-; Institute for Historical Review; White Patriot Party
- Documented Organizations, 1940s-2000s; 1
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes materials collected from different groups and organizations monitored by the SPLC Intelligence Project. It has been arranged into subseries by creating organization; within each subseries, materials range from catalogs and ephemeral mailings to pamphlets or publications by the group. Only scattered serials are present in this collection. For information about other serials published by monitored groups and collected by SPLC, consult the library's online catalog.
  - A Way Out, 1
    - Literature, 1983 (Box 1)
      General note
      Belton
      Scope and Contents note
      Newsletter printout.
      Missouri
  - A-Albionic Consulting and Research, 2
    - Mass mailings, catalogs, 1985 (Box 1)
      Ferndale
      Update on "The Project;" booklists.
      Michigan
  - Abiding Truth Ministries, 3
    - Mass mailings, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Adventures Unlimited, 4
    - Catalog, 2004 (Box 1)
      Kempton
      Illinois
    - Mass mailings, 1998 (Box 1)
      Anaheim
      California
  - Aesthetic Realism Foundation, 5
    - Literature, 1991 (Box 1)
      New York
      Excerpts from "The Right of Aesthetic Realism to be Known" periodical.
      New York (N.Y.)
  - Aid and Abet Foundation, 6
    - Literature, mass mailings, 2005 and undated (Box 1)
      Phoenix
      Includes Special Police Officer bulletins, "Citizens Rule Book," and fliers.
      Arizona
  - A.K.I.A. Publications, 7
    - Literature, mass mailings, 1983 (Box 1)
      Hayden Lake
      Sample newsletter and subscription letter for "Inter-Klan Newsletter and Survival Alert."
      Idaho
  - Alabama White Knights of the Ku Klux Klan, 8
    - Literature, undated (Box 1)
      Huntsville
      Includes "Official Kloran."
      Alabama
  - Alamo Christian Churches, 9
    - Literature, undated (Box 1)
      Alma
      Includes pamphlet, "Genocide: Treaty, FBI, and the Neo-Nazis," undated.
      Arkansas
  - Alert Americans Association/Christian Book Store, 10
    - Mass mailings, 1986 (Box 1)
      Cape Canaveral
      Florida
  - All Source Systems, 11
    - All Source Digest bulletins, catalogs, 1980s (Box 1)
      Seattle
      Washington
  - Alpha Omega Resources, 12
    - Catalog, 1999 (Box 1)
      Mullett Lake
  - Alpha Publications, 13
    - Catalog, 1989 (Box 1)
      Sharon Center
      Ohio
  - Amazing Facts, 14
    - Literature, catalogs, 1999 and undated (Box 1)
      Roseville
      Includes Amazing Facts Study Guide, undated.
  - America Alert Program, 15
    - Literature, undated (Box 1)
      Wilson
      Includes pamphlets on Christian education and Church vs. State.
      North Carolina
  - America First Committee, 16
    - Literature, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
      Chicago
      Includes anti-semetic and pro-white pamphlets.
  - America Today Publishers, 17
    - Catalogs, 1996-1997 (Box 1)
      Houston
  - America's Promise/Lord Covenant Church, 18
    - Bible Law Index, undated (Box 1)
      Sandpoint
    - Literature, 1995-1997 and undated (Box 1)
      Includes pamphlets by Dave Barley, such as "Separatism Into Restoration," "Vaccinations: A Mark of the Beast," "Martin Luther and the Jews," "The City of the Living God," along with newsletters and other handouts.
    - Catalogs, 1980s-1990s (Box 1)
  - American's Bulletin, 19
    - Mass mailings, 1995-1996 (Box 1)
      Central Point
      Oregon
  - American Constitutionalist League, 20
    - Literature, 1994 (Box 1)
      Photocopy of Operation Plan (OPLAN) American Viper.
  - American Free Press, 21
    - Literature, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
      Special reports: "Billions for the Bankers, Debts for the People" (2001) and "8 Reasons Why the Budget is a Fraud" (2002).
      Washington (D.C.)
  - American Knights of the Ku Klux Klan, 22
    - Publicity, 1997 (Box 1)
      Ironwood
      Klan rally advertisement.
  - American Mercury Magazine, 23
    - Sept. 1960 issue (Box 1)
  - American Israelite Fellowship, 24
    - Literature, 1987-1988 and undated (Box 1)
      Waynesville
      Excerpts from "Crusader" serial, other publicity.
  - American Nationalist Federation/The Kingdom Ministry, 25
    - Literature, 1980s (Box 1)
      Lawrenceville
      Photocopies of newsletters; "The Real Hate Group," by Pete Peters; "God and Lincoln on Negro-White Marriages" pamphlet; "Citizens Rule Book," and ANF promotional literature.
      Georgia
  - American Nazi Party, 26
    - Literature and mass mailings, 1980s-1990s (Box 1)
      Fliers, etc.
    - Field Manual, 1989 (Box 1)
  - American Patriot Fax Network, 27
    - Faxes, 1995 (Box 1)
      Nevada
  - The American Sentinel, 28
    - Reports, undated (Box 1)
      Charlotte
      "Eight Free Reports" issued by American Sentinel.
  - American Survival Party, 29
    - Literature, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
      New York City
      Photocopied excerpts of American Survival Papers.
  - American Vision, 30
    - Biblical Worldview excerpts, 1998-2000 (Box 1)
      Atlanta
      Photocopies.
  - American Workers Party-National Socialist Movement, 31
    - Literature excerpts, undated (Box 1)
      Bethlehem
      Photocopies of "Social Justice."
      Pennsylvania
  - Americans Against Arms to Israel, 32
    - Mass mailings, 1980s (Box 1)
      Includes blank National Opinion Poll on Middle East Issues.
  - Americans for Action, 33
    - Catalog, 1985
      Altadena
      "Midnight Messenger" catalog.
  - Angelus Press, 34
    - Catalog, 2004
      Kansas City
  - Anglo-Saxon Christian Patriots, 35
    - Literature, 1980s
      Snellville
  - Anti-Lawyer Party, 36
    - Literature, undated (Box 1)
      Antioch
      Introductory pamphlet.
  - Appalachian Forum, 37
    - Catalogs, clippings, 1980s
      Pittsburgh
  - Arizona Caucus Club, 38
    - Catalog, 1984
      Mesa
  - ARS Publications, 39
    - Printouts, 2003 (Box 1)
      Livingston
      New Jersey
  - Artisan Sales, 40
    - Catalog, 1980 (Box 1)
      Thousand Oaks
  - Aryan Nations, 41
    - unspecified (Box 1)
      See Church of Jesus Christ Christian.
  - Aryan Racial Loyalist Party, 42
    - Literature, 1991 (Box 1)
      Zanesville
      Short stories by Jack Grimes, including "Yonder Comes the Jungle," "The Dictator and the State," "What I Did During the War," "The Little Man," "Why I Became an Anti-Semite," "Ivan the Indian Killer," and "The Klan and the Kike."
  - Aryan Youth Movement, 43
    - Literature, 1981 (Box 1)
      Sacramento
      "Revolutionary Recruitment Issue" newspaper insert.
  - Assemblies of God, 44
    - Literature, undated (Box 1)
      Springfield
      Photocopied pamphlet: "Santa Claus, the Easter Bunny, and Jesus."
  - Atlan Formularies, 45
    - Catalog, undated (Box 1)
      Harrison
      Survival catalog.
  - The Barnes Review, 46
    - Literature, 2000s (Box 1)
    - Mass mailings, catalogs, 2002-2008 (Box 1)
  - Barristers Inn, 47
    - Mass mailings, catalogs, 1986 (Box 1)
      Boise
      Advertisements, photocopies.
  - Bea Lydecker's Naturals, Inc., 48
    - Catalog, undated (Box 1)
      Oregon City
  - Bible Sabbath Association, 49
    - Literature, catalogs, 1992 (Box 1)
      Fairview
      Oklahoma
  - Biblical Enterprises, Inc., 50
    - Literature, 1997-2006 (Box 1)
      Langley
      Pamphlets by Bob LeRoy.
  - Big Show Journal, 51
    - Catalog, 2000 (Box 1)
      Iola
      Wisconsin
  - Blood Axis, 52
    - Literature, 1993 (Box 1)
      Denver
      Colorado
  - Blue Press, 53
    - Catalog, 2006 (Box 1)
      Scottsdale
  - Bohica Concepts, 54
    - Catalogs, 1990s-2000s; 3 folders (Box 1)
      Randle
  - Brigade Quartermasters, 55
    - Catalog, 2004 (Box 1)
      Kennesaw
  - British Nationalist Party, 56
    - Literature, mass mailings, 1999-2002 (Box 2)
      London
      Includes materials from the American Friends organization, based in Falls Church, VA. Photocopies of BNP-AF publications.
      United Kingdom
  - British Patriot, 57
    - Literature, 1995 (Box 2)
      Torquay
      Photocopy of Issue 12.
  - Camp War Paint Inc., 58
    - Literature, undated (Box 2)
      Ash Flat
      Paintball flier.
  - Campus Review (University of Iowa), 59
    - Literature, 1990 (Box 2)
      Iowa City
      "Daily Idiot" issue.
      Iowa
  - Capital Information Association, 60
    - Literature, 1984 (Box 2)
      Ann Arbor
      Newsletter excerpts.
  - Carolina Knights of the Ku Klux Klan, 61
    - Mass mailings, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
      Angier
      Includes letter from Glenn Miller declaring candidacy for state office.
  - Cedade, 62
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 2)
      Barcelona
      Includes letter seeking photographs of Klan activities.
      Spain
  - Censored, 63
    - Mass mailings, undated (Box 2)
      Bonita Springs
      Excerpt from Censored Magazine
  - Chalcedon Foundation, 64
    - Mass mailings, 2000s (Box 2)
      Vallecito
  - Chalcedon Presbyrterian Church, 65
    - Literature, 1999-2000 (Box 2)
      Photocopies of "The Counsel."
  - Champions of Reason, 66
    - Research file, 1993 (Box 2)
      SPLC photocopies of Champions of Reason coverage.
  - Charles Martel Society, 67
    - Mass mailings, 2005 (Box 2)
      "Occidental Quarterly" mass mailings.
    - Literature, 2004 (Box 2)
      "Occidental Quarterly" monograph no. 1, "Understanding Jewish Influence."
  - Chick Publications, 68
    - Literature, 1977-1982 (Box 2)
      Chino
      The Crusaders, volumes 8, 12-14.
  - Christ's Gospel Fellowship Church, 69
    - Literature, 1997 and undated (Box 2)
      Spokane
      Pathfinder pamphlets.
  - Christian American Advocates, 70
    - Literature, catalogs, 1988 and undated (Box 2)
      Mooreland
  - Christian American Research League, 71
    - Mass mailings, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Christian Anti-Communist Crusade, 72
    - Literature, 1982 (Box 2)
      Long Beach
  - Christian Bible Ministries, 73
    - Literature, catalogs, 2001 (Box 2)
      Christianburg
      Ecclesia reports.
      Virginia
  - Christian Civil Liberties Association, 74
    - Literature, catalogs, 1994-1995 (Box 2)
      Afton
      Tennessee
  - Christian Conservative Churches of America, 75
    - Literature, 1976 and undated (Box 2)
      Flora
      Membership applications, essays.
  - Christian Defense League, 76
    - Mass mailings, 1987-1997 (Box 2)
      Arabi
      Louisiana
  - Christian Justice Party, 77
    - Literature, 1989 (Box 2)
      Manila
      Coalition (with Flying Tigers Party and Plebisite Party) literature.
      Philippines
  - Christian Kingdom Publications, 78
    - Literature, 1995-1996 (Box 2)
      Institute
      Pamphlets titled "Hope Deferred, or Hope Fulfilled?" and "Where Are They Now?"
      West Virginia
  - Christian Liberty Academy, 79
    - Literature, 1994 (Box 2)
      Arlington Heights
      "Christian Educator" photocopies.
  - Christian Nationalist White People's Party, 80
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2)
      Portland
      Letter to Klanwatch from Michael Hansen.
  - Christian Patriot Association, 81
    - Literature, catalogs, 1999 (Box 2)
      Boring
      Includes information on the Natural Coin Exchange.
  - Christian Patriots Defense League, 82
    - Literature, 1984-1986 (Box 2)
      Reports, etc.
  - Christian Research, 83
    - Literature, catalogs, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
      Eureka Springs
  - Christian Separatist Church, 84
    - Literature, 1993-1995 (Box 2)
      Kodak
      Church documentation and pamphlets by Pastor V.S. Herrell, including "The Justification of God" and "The Racial War at Baal-Peor: A Study in Pornos."
  - Christian Vanguard, 85
    - Catalog, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Church of America, 86
    - Mass mailings, 1990s (Box 2)
      Elkins
  - Church of God Evangelic Association, 87
    - Mass mailings, 1990s-2000s (Box 2)
      Waxahachie
      Materials related to Newswatch Magazine.
      Texas
  - Church of Israel, 88
    - Literature, undated (Box 2)
      "Articles of Faith and Doctrine," Diocese of Manasseh.
  - Church of Jesus Christ, 89
    - Literature, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
      Writings by Thomas Robb; some excerpts from "Message of Old."
  - Church of Jesus Christ Christian-Aryan Nations, 90
    - Mass mailings, 1990s (Box 2)
    - Literature, 1980s (Box 2)
      Aryan Nations pamphlets, including "A Story of the Original Ku Klux Klan," "We Have Accomplished Our Goal," "Life Law," "The Aryan Warrior," "The Secret Holocaust," "The Pharisees," "To Lose Our Sovereignty," and a copy of "Teutonic Unity."
    - Literature, undated (Box 2)
      Photocopies of bulletins and pamphlets, including "God, Man, Nations, and the Races," "The Bible Answers Racial Questions," "What Happened to Cain?," "You: Before the World Was Framed," and other excerpts.
  - Church of Jesus Christ Christian of Montana, 91
    - Catalog, 1994 (Box 2)
      Noxon
      Four Horsemen Press.
      Montana
    - Literature, 1993-1995 (Box 2)
      "Our Purpose, Our Mission," and other printouts.
  - Church of the Creator, 92
    - Literature, undated (Box 2)
      Otto
  - Citizens Alert, 93
    - Literature, 2002 (Box 2)
      Blountsville
      Special issue.
  - Citizens for Foreign Aid Reform, 94
    - Literature, 1989 (Box 2)
      Rexdale
      Excerpts from Quarterly Reports.
      Canada (ON)
  - Civilian Guard, 95
    - Literature, 1983 (Box 2)
      Middlesboro
      Photocopied information sheets, organizational charts.
      Kentucky
  - Coalition of Concerned Citizens Working for the Rights of America, 96
    - Literature, 1995 (Box 2)
      Curlew
      "Action News," Vol. 1.1, photocopy.
  - Colony Press, 97
    - Literature, 1997 (Box 2)
      Ewing
      "World Colony News" photocopy.
  - Confederate Hammer Skins/Confederate White Vikings, 98
    - Literature, 1990s (Box 2)
      Dallas
      Photocopies of fliers, other promotional items.
  - Confederate Knights of the Ku Klux Klan, 99
    - Literature, 1990-1996 (Box 2)
      Henderson
  - Confederate National Congress, 100
    - Literature, undated (Box 2)
      Raleigh
      Central Office Bulletin.
  - Connecticut Education Association, 101
    - Literature, 1981 (Box 2)
      Hartford
      Resource materials on the KKK.
      Connecticut
  - Conservative Citizens Foundation, 102
    - Mass mailing, 1999 (Box 2)
      St. Louis
  - Council of Conservative Citizens, 103
    - Literature, undated (Box 2)
  - Crowhurst, Norman, 104
    - Literature, 1980s (Box 2)
      "Christian Tax Payment" forms.
  - Crusade Against Corruption, 105
    - Literature, undated (Box 2)
      Marietta
      Photocopied excerpt.
  - Crusade for Christ and Country, 106
    - Literature, 1990s-2000s and undated (Box 2)
      Little Rock
      Includes articles and pamphlets by Col. Jack Mohr. Mohr's organization is also referred to as Crusades for Christ, and he published in both Bay St. Louis, Mississippi, and Little Rock, Arkansas. Titles in this folder include "The Marvelous Epistle of Romans," "This Time Bomb Called Zionism," "From the Watchman's Corner!," and others.
    - Literature, 1990s-2000s and undated (Box 2)
      Includes booklets and pamphlets by Jack Mohr, such as "Seed of Satan: Literal or Figurative?," "The Birthright or the Right to Govern," "Signs and Wonders!," "Firearms and Freedom!," "Conspiracy to Deceive the Elect!!," "A Warning Direct from the Horse's Mouth!," "Exploding the 'Chosen People' Myth," "The Psychopolitical Indoctrination of America!," "Battle for the Truth," "Salt Without Savor!" and others.
  - Crusador, 107
    - Catalogs, 2005-2006 (Box 2)
      Orlando
  - C.S.A. Enterprises, 108
    - Literature, 1980s (Box 2)
      Pontiac
      "CSA" refers to "The Covenant, the Sword, the Arm of the Lord." File includes photocopied literature such as the Christian Army Basic Training Manual and "Prepare War" pamphlet.
  - Cyngus Business Media, 109
    - Literature, 2006 (Box 2)
      Fort Atkinson
      Law Enforcement Technology media guide.
  - David Duke Report, 110
    - Mass mailings, 2000-2008 (Box 2)
      Mandeville
    - Catalogs, 2002-2004 (Box 2)
      Book advertisements and order forms.
  - Delta Force, 111
    - Catalogs, 1999-2003 (Box 2)
      El Dorado
  - Dixie Outfitters, 112
    - Catalogs, 2003 (Box 2)
      Odom
  - Donald Kimball and Co., 113
    - Mass mailings, 1987 (Box 2)
      Fayette
  - Ediciones UDECAN, 114
    - Literature, 1970s (Box 3)
      Library of Political Secrets booklets: "The Secret Driving Force of Communism," "What is Judaism?".
      Mexico
  - 11th Hour Remnant Messenger, 115
    - Literature, 1990s-2000 (Box 3)
      "The Seven Year Tribulation of Daniel and Revelation," with other pamphlets and fliers.
  - Emergency Essentials, 116
    - Catalogs, 1999 (Box 3)
      Orem
      Utah
  - Emissary Publications, 117
    - Catalogs, 1990-1998 (Box 3)
      Clackamas
  - Eugenics Society of Northern California, 118
    - Literature, 1950s (Box 3)
      Fragments of Eugenics Pamphlets, undated.
  - Euro-American Alliance, 119
    - Literature, undated (Box 3)
      Milwaukee
      Essays and reports, including "Germany: Hotbed of the Mafia," "The Talmud: Bible of the So-Called Jews," "The Myth of a White Jewish Race," and some excerpts from The Talon.
  - European American Educational Association, 120
    - Literature, 1995 (Box 3)
      Eastpointe
      Photocopy of the organization's newsletter.
  - FAIR/Fairness and Accuracy in Reporting, 121
    - Mass mailings, 1996 (Box 3)
      Press release faxes.
  - Faith Baptist Church and Ministries, 122
    - Literature, mass mailings, 1995 and 2003 (Box 3)
  - Family Heritage Books, 123
    - Literature, 1996 and 1998 (Box 3)
      Thomaston
      "America: Superpower of Prophecy" and "A Time for Joy."
  - Farmers and Consumers Report, 124
    - Literature, 1990 (Box 3)
      Gering
      Various reports and excerpts.
      Nebraska
  - Farmers Liberation Army, 125
    - Literature, undated (Box 3)
      Flier announcing and explaining the organization.
  - Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR), 126
    - Research file, 2005 (Box 3)
      Article mentioning FAIR collected by SPLC.
  - First Amendment Books and Video, 127
    - Catalog, 2004 (Box 3)
  - The First Freedom, 128
    - Mass mailings, printouts, 2002-2004 (Box 3)
      Silverhill
      Website printouts, newspaper inserts.
  - Flatland Books, 129
    - Catalog, 1998 (Box 3)
      Fort Bragg
  - Florida Foundation to Fight Corruption, 130
    - Literature, 1997 (Box 3)
      Tallahassee
      "Corruption Chronicles" sample edition.
  - Free Son Publishing, 131
    - Literature, 1989 (Box 3)
      Tacoma
      Anonymous booklet, "Land of the Free?."
  - Freemen Against Collective Tyranny (FACT), 132
    - Catalog, undated (Box 3)
      Canyon Country
  - Die Freikorpsmann Presse, 133
    - Mass mailing, 1994 (Box 3)
      Victoria
      "Jew Watch" insert.
  - Gadsden Minutemen, 134
    - Literature, 1994-1996 (Box 3)
      Attalla
      Meeting materials, photocopies of newsletters.
  - Georgia Arms, 135
    - Catalogs, 1999-2000 (Box 3)
      Villa Rica
  - German American National Public Affairs Committee, 136
    - Literature, 1997-1998 (Box 3)
      Pensacola
      GANPAC fliers and a copy of "The Genocide of the German People."
  - German Citizen's Initiative, 137
    - Literature, mass mailings, 1980s (Box 3)
      Buffalo
      "Teutonic Unity" literature, other mass mailings.
  - Golden Mean Society, 138
    - Literature, mass mailings, 1985 (Box 3)
      Issues of the GMS "Journal-Report," other mailings.
  - Golden Mean Team, 139
    - Mass mailings, 1990 and undated (Box 3)
      Missoula
  - Gospel of Christ Kingdom Church-National Chaplain's Association, 140
    - Literature, 1991 (Box 3)
      Hayden